PEDRO MEDINA ROBLES

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE: 13260429

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PHP (OOP) Composer JAVA MySQL MariaDB

jSON GIT UML

HTML5, JS CSS3 AVANZADO A1AX

jQuery WebApps (Angular) Bootstrap

Visual Basic.Net (Windows Forms) Windows Server, Linux Server

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative
Organized
Results oriented
Tenacious

CONTACT

9371678906 pedro.medina.ro97@outlook.com Col. Tascoob Street River Mezcalapa Block 3 #8 CP.86500, H.Cárdenas, Tabasco GitHub: <u>PedroMedina97</u>

OTHER ABILITIES

TECHNICAL SUPPORT FOR
COMPUTER EQUIPMENT
-NETWORKS
-SERVERS
-MICROSOFT OFFICE COMPLETE
-PHOTOSHOP, ILLUSTRATOR,
PREMIERE PRO (BASIC)

IDIOMAS

English B2 conversational

COURSES | TRAININGS

BOOTSTRAP

UDEMY

PHP

UDEMY

JAVASCRIPT, NODE JS, ANGULAR, JQUERY

UDEMY

ABOUT ME

I am a Computer Systems Engineer graduated from the Universidad del Valle de Mexico, I have worked on projects in the corporate sector, oil, automotive, agricultural and recently administrative accounting integrating map technologies, REDUX patterns, Angular, PHP, Node.js so my skills are of a Full Stack Developer, but I can perform without problems as Back End or Front End.

EXPERIENCE

PROFESSIONAL CONSULTANT SERVICES

NTTDATA - CITI | JULY. 2024 - OCTOBER. 2024 (PARTIAL)

FIGMA-based Template Development
API web services consumption
Development of re-usable components in ANGULAR
Bootstrap
KANBAN, DevOps, Agile, SCRUM

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

KOUD | August. 2023 - August. 2024

FIGMA-based Template Development
API web services consumption
Development of re-usable components in ANGULAR
REDUX
CSS and SCSS animation development
Maps (Leaflet)
Bootstrap, Materialize
KANBAN, DevOps, Agile, SCRUM

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING ASSISTANT

IPS GROUP | FEBRUARY, 2022 - MARCH, 2023

Development and consumption of REST API services (PHP)
Library integration (Composer)
Databases (MySQL, MariaDB)
Front-End Development (Angular, jQuery)
Technical support to internal and remote users
Process improvement
Planning with Microsoft Project, SCRUM, Jira Software

PROJECT LEADER / JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

Xinergia Group | NOVIEMBRE 2019 - ENERO. 2022

Overall project management using agile methodologies (SCRUM)
Project and deliverables planning with Microsoft Project
Dashboard management
Analyzing and documenting information from client minutes
Use of digital communication and file transfer tools
Relational database modeling
Design of process, flow and UML diagrams
Web design (Angular Framework, Bootstrap)
API's development and integration

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

Universidad del Valle de México | 2016 - 2021